Kettle and Idol
This is because you have a reputation for Instagram and so on.
Yes, I think clothes are self-expression.
Clothing is self-expression, expressing yourself.
That's right.
Smile is the best makeup.
The best makeup.
Clothing is self-expression
Let's hear your definition.
Before I started performing.
I was very shy when I was little.
That's right.
I used to think it was really impossible to speak in front of people like this.
That's one of the reasons I started performing.
I became interested in clothes.
I've always been interested in my own taste.
When I wear my favorite taste or my favorite line of clothes
I get more excited
And it gives me confidence.
I can be myself as I am.
And gradually, I started to wear clothes
I'm wearing what I like.
I can be myself a little more.
I see.
I have that kind of thing.
I'm not good in front of people in many ways.
Clothes.
The way you look at it.
When you have a way of looking at things...
I can express myself as I am
I can express myself in front of the camera.
Yes, sir.
After that, it's all about clothes.
I've come to love dressing up.
I've come to really like it.
I hope I can use it again in my work.
I see.
When I started this job, I realized that...
You see...
The stylists and stuff...
They bring me beautiful outfits.
I think that's
Self-expression
It makes you excited, doesn't it?
It does.
Oh, that's nice.
So if you get your makeup done the same way...
Also...
It would be nice.
That's nice.
It's a calling.
It really is a calling, isn't it?
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad you said that.
I'm really glad.
I see. At an entertainment agency.
I'm glad.
When you say it like that...
I'd go shopping with my mom.
I'd go shopping with my seniors.
Your mother, of course.
She loves clothes, too.
She wears a lot of them together.
That's why...
Among the Eriki members, Sakurai-san...
Do you think she's fashionable?
Even if they're your seniors?
Is it hard to say?
No.
I think Riko is very stylish.
Hee...
She's cute.
How old are you now?
Twenty-two.
Twenty-two?
Oh, I see.
Do you talk about that, too?
We talk about clothes.
Clothes.
See you next week!
Okay, well, that's fashionable.
Let's see...
Self-expression
Fashion is self-expression
Yes, sir.
That's great.
By the way...
Did your mother give that to you, too?
I did.
Oh, you got it from yourself?
That's great.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm not a good student.
I'm not a good student, but I think I'm pretty good in that area.
That's right.
I think so.
But you're saying that?
You know, to Maya Maya and stuff.
I said it for the first time today.I said it for the first time today.
Come on, say it.
Maya Maya.
I...
I think clothes are a form of self-expression.
If I say...
I think she'll say, "Ah.
I'd like you to say it.
Then I'll say it.
By all means.
Is there anything that's popular among your friends right now?
What's the word...
This program is for the Joban Family.
Mr. Kiddos
Mr. Monta Mr. Sukasa
Thank you very much.